(Bernadette:)Hey, Raj.
(Raj:)Hey, I got you
a little gift.
(Bernadette:)Oh, that's a lot
of Girl Scout Cookies.
(Raj:)You know me.
I'm from India.
(Raj:)I can't resist children begging.
(Raj:)So, how's it going
with the title to the house?
(Howard:)Great, it's all done.
(Howard:)The lawyer
tracked down my father
(Howard:)and got him to sign it over.
(Howard:)I didn't have to meet him,
I didn't have to talk to him,
(Howard:)I don't even know where he is.
(Raj:)Wow, so you're not curious
at all?
(Howard:)Nope.
Hm. What if he's in prison?
(Raj:)What if he's a spy?
(Raj:)What if he's
in a Beatles cover band?
(Raj:)I'm just saying, if he's got
your nose and haircut,
(Raj:)he'd make a killer Ringo.
(Wil Wheaton:)Thanks again for
agreeing to do this.
Oh, it's cool; I've never been
on a podcast before.
(Leonard:)Well, you picked
a good one to start.
(Leonard:)Wil's had lots of great guests.
(Leonard:)Jonathan Frakes, Brent Spiner,
(Leonard:)Michael Dorn, Gates McFadden...
Those are Star Trek people.
Yes!